Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives, 1905 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2004; UA176.002; 5.0 Linear Feet
  - Sports, Fall and Spring, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00018; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00019; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00020; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00021; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00022; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00023; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00024; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse - ECAC, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00025; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00026; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse - ECAC, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00027; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00028; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Practices, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00029; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Sailing, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00030; Heller, Eric (Box 9)
    - Sailing, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00031; Heller, Eric (Box 9)
    - Sailing, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00032; Heller, Eric (Box 9)
    - Men's Soccer vs. Bently, 1987; UA176.002.009.00001.00033; Lesser, Adam (Box 9)
    - Men's Soccer, 1987; UA176.002.009.00001.00034; Dower, Denise (Box 9)
    - Men's Soccer, 1987; UA176.002.009.00001.00035; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Men's Soccer, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00036; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Men's Soccer, 1987; UA176.002.009.00001.00037; Rashid, Kristine (Box 9)
    - Men's Soccer, 1987; UA176.002.009.00001.00038; Wajsezuk, W. (Box 9)
    - Women's Softball, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00039; De la Cruz, Cedric (Box 9)
    - Softball, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00040; De la Cruz, Cedric (Box 9)
    - Softball, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00041; Heller, Eric (Box 9)
    - Tennis, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00042; Sandberg, Stacia (Box 9)
    - Men's Tennis, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00043; Sklar, H. (Box 9)
    - Men's Tennis, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00044; Epstien, Jon (Box 9)
    - Men's Tennis, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00045; Epstien, Jon (Box 9)
    - Men's Tennis, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00046; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Men's Track, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00047; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Men's Track, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00048; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Track NCAA III Smith Champs, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00049; Stevens, C. (Box 9)
    - Track, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00050; Sklar, H. (Box 9)
    - Track, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00051 (Box 9)
    - Track, 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00052; Sklar, H. (Box 9)
    - Track, 1987 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00001.00053 (Box 9)
  - All Categories, Spring and Fall, 1986 -- 1988; UA176.002.009.00002
    - Maureen & Marina, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00001; O'Brien, Mo (Box 9)
    - Students and Faculty, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00002 (Box 9)
    - Music Group, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00003 (Box 9)
    - Rally, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00004; O'Brien, Mo (Box 9)
    - Sommerville Theater, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00005; O'Brien, Mo (Box 9)
    - Sommerville Theater, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00006; O'Brien, Mo (Box 9)
    - Students/Matriculation/Lunch/Tuftspeak # 1, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00007; Dower, Denise (Box 9)
    - Matriculation, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00008; Dower, Denise (Box 9)
    - Apple Jam-music, 1986; UA176.002.009.00002.00009; Stevens, Chris (Box 9)
    - Basketball (Men), 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00010; Sklar, Howard (Box 9)
    - Faculty Waits on You Meal, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00011; Dower, Denise (Box 9)
    - Field Hockey (Women) & Soccer (Women), 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00012; Vitale, Karen (Box 9)
    - Merry-go-round, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00013; Dower, Denise (Box 9)
    - Mary Cyr, employee of Nov. & others, 1988; UA176.002.009.00002.00014; Dower, Denise (Box 9)
  - Features and News, Fall, 1905 -- 1989; UA176.002.010.00001
    - ACLU Drive, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00001; Newman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Aerobics, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00002; Bensoner, Mark (Box 10)
    - Anthony J.; Afro Am. Talent Show, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00003; O'Brien, M/ Drower, D. (Box 10)
    - Afro Am. Talent Show, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00004; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - AIDS Panel, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00005; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - AIDS Info Tables, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00006; Kittredge, Wendy (Box 10)
    - AIDS Info Tables, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00007; Eisenberg, Laura (Box 10)
    - AIDS Quilt Lecture, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00008; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Pam Allara, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00009; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Apple Jam - the Blue Lites, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00010; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Alvin Ailey Dance, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00011; Ross, Linda (Box 10)
    - Alpha Phi Seesaw-a-thon, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00012; Hertschel, Sam (Box 10)
    - Yahuda Amichai, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00013; Starr, Ron (Box 10)
    - Animal Rights Day, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00014; Ross, Linda (Box 10)
    - Answering Machine, 1986; UA176.002.010.00001.00015; Braren, Paul (Box 10)
    - The Answering Machine, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00016; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Apple Jam - Nova Xpress, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00017; Kulukundis, Natali (Box 10)
    - A & S Faculty Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00018; Michaelman, Scott (Box 10)
    - Music group, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00019 (Box 10)
    - Peggy Barrett, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00020; Michaelman, Scott (Box 10)
    - Battle of the Bands, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00021; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Candide, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00022; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Frosh Move-in, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00023; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Frosh Move-in, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00024; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Frosh Move-in, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00025; Bielle, Joelle (Box 10)
    - Frosh Move-in; Lunch on Pres. Lawn, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00026; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Frosh Move-in, 1931; UA176.002.010.00001.00027; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Jewel Bell - Afro American, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00028; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - HC Bubs, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00029; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - B & G Protest Ballou, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00030; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - B & G Protest Ballou, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00031; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - B & G Protest Ballou, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00032; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - B & G Protests, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00033; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Blood Drive; After hours, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00034; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Boston Baked Comedy Theater, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00035; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - On Broadway-Weekender, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00036; Friend of Alex (Box 10)
    - Bromfield-Pearson, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00037; Kulukundis, Natali (Box 10)
    - Bubs; Jills; Mates in Goddard, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00038; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Spring Fling, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00039; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Cars on Fire at Oval, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00040; Dequattro, John (Box 10)
    - Chaplaincy Wessel Exhibit, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00041 (Box 10)
    - Cheap Sox, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00042; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Chinese Cooking, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00043; Eisenberg, Laura (Box 10)
    - Chorale, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00044; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Chowder Fest, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00045; Feldman, Melissa (Box 10)
    - Brett Clemmer-IGC Direct, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00046; Chatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Club LVS, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00047; Newman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Professor Colcord, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00048; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Professor Colcord, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00049; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Condom Dispenser, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00050; O'Brien, M (Box 10)
    - Contra Speakers, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00051; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Contra Speakers, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00052; Graymel, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Convocation, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00053; Drower, D. (Box 10)
    - Crafts House, 1987; UA176.002.010.00001.00054; Stevens, C. (Box 10)
    - Crafts House Fire, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00055; Stevens, C. (Box 10)
    - Crafts House Investigation, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00056; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - CSL, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00057; Condon, Jeff (Box 10)
    - Curtis Intersection, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00058; Kittredge, Wendy (Box 10)
    - John Cutler, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00059; Scheidl, Peter (Box 10)
    - Daily Fall MVPs, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00060; Stevens, C/, Starr, Ron/ Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Daily Football, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00061 (Box 10)
    - Greg Davis - ZBT President, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00062; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Identity Crisis, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00063; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Dewick Fire, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00064; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Dewick Fire, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00065; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Dining Hall Overcrowding, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00066; Rascher, Andrew (Box 10)
    - Diversity Panel, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00067; Starr, Ron (Box 10)
    - Divestment & Voter Registration, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00068; Feldman, Melissa (Box 10)
    - Dukakis Preparation, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00069; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00070; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00071; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00072; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00073; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00074; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00075; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00076; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Dukakis at Tufts, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00077; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Duke, 1987; UA176.002.010.00001.00078; Lesser, Adam (Box 10)
    - Earth day, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00079 (Box 10)
    - Eaton Cafe, 1986; UA176.002.010.00001.00080; Brarer, Paul (Box 10)
    - Empire Builders, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00081; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Employee of the Month, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00082; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Engineer Speech, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00083; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Environmental Lecture, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00084; Ross, Linda (Box 10)
    - Environmental House, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00085; Starr, Ron (Box 10)
    - Environmental Symposium Organizers, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00086; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Environmental Symposium, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00087; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00088; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00089; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00090; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Fashion Show, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00091; Blackburn, Ron (Box 10)
    - Professor Fawaz, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00092; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Mary Ella Feinlieb, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00093; Ross, Linda (Box 10)
    - Fire-Cambridge, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00094; Hertschel, Sam (Box 10)
    - D. Flanders, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00095; Poisey (Box 10)
    - Fletcher Students, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00096; Buckman, Laura (Box 10)
    - Frat Busting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00097; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Fraternities, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00098; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Matt Freedman, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00099; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - French Professor Kendgon, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00100; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Galantic, Ivan, 1986; UA176.002.010.00001.00101; Braren, Paul/Eisenberg, Sharen (Box 10)
    - Gallery II, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00102; Ross, Linda (Box 10)
    - Tufts Club; Emmanuel Gardner, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00103; Michaelman, Scott (Box 10)
    - Prof. John Gibson, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00104 (Box 10)
    - Gravity Stone, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00105; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - 1st Annual Greek Olympics, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00106; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Halloween on Hill, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00107; Stevens, Chris (Box 10)
    - West Hall Halloween Party, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00108; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - West Hall Halloween Party, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00109; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Mary Harris - Study Abroad, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00110; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Head of the Charles, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00111; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Hero of the Charles, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00112; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Head of the Charles, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00113; Allen, Eleanor (Box 10)
    - Head of the Charles, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00114 (Box 10)
    - High Street Cafe--Weekender, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00115; Barbara (Box 10)
    - Hillside Liquors --Add, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00116 (Box 10)
    - Homecoming, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00117; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Homecoming Nominees, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00118; Herschel, Sam (Box 10)
    - Block Party, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00119; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Homecoming Float Parade & Tailgating, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00120; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Homecoming: Tailgating & Crowd Shots, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00121; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Homecoming Nominees, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00122; Herschel, Sam (Box 10)
    - Homecoming Block Party, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00123; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Random Homecoming, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00124; Polack, Marina (Box 10)
    - Homecoming Block Party & Pep Rally, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00125; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Homecoming--Smoker Tufts Club, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00126; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Hot Tuna, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00127; Newman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Homecoming--Jius & Mates, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00128; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - I-Tones; Shy 5 at Pub, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00129; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - I.D.C. '88-'89, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00130; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Senator Inoye, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00131; Eisenberg, Laura (Box 10)
    - Mary Lee Jacobs--Gen. Council for UNIX, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00132; Eisenberg, Laura (Box 10)
    - Billy Jackson, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00133; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Jazz Ghost Band, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00134; Rascher, Andrew (Box 10)
    - Jills and Marks Practice, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00135; Labouitz, Bill (Box 10)
    - Rona Johnson, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00136; Kulukundis, Natali (Box 10)
    - Paul Joseph, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00137; Rascher, Andrew (Box 10)
    - Jim Kelley, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00138; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Marcia Kelly--SA Director, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00139; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Kids on Campus for Halloween, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00140; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - A Man/Professor, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00141; Ladd, Dean (Box 10)
    - LCS Blood Drive, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00142; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Leonan Symposium 11:15/4:00, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00143; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Lecture --9, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00144; Michaelman, Scott (Box 10)
    - Lufkin Library, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00145; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Lunch on lawn/Matriculation, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00146; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Marsells & 4 tops, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00147; Stevens, Chris (Box 10)
    - Murry Martin--Head Librarian, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00148; Rascher, Andrew (Box 10)
    - Matriculation, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00149; Sklar, Howard (Box 10)
    - Matriculation, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00150; Bielle, Joelle (Box 10)
    - Max Creek at Pub, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00151; Herschel, Sam (Box 10)
    - A Man/Professor, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00152; Maxwell, Dean/Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Dean Mayer Press Conference, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00153; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Mayer at Campus Center, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00154; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Mayer Press Conference, 1989; UA176.002.010.00001.00155; Rashid, Kristine (Box 10)
    - Mayer at Daily/06. Press Conference, Outdoor scenes, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00156; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - McCullester HSR, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00157; Kulukundis, Natali (Box 10)
    - Medford Youth Festival, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00158; Stevens, Chris (Box 10)
    - Media Panel, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00159; Newman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Mark Bronson; Misc., 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00160 (Box 10)
    - Monkey Bars; the only shoot that showed, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00161; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Monte Carlo Night, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00162; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Moskito Indian (Latin American collective), 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00163; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Natalie Di Natalio, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00164; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Obstacle Course, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00165; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Occupational Therapy Lecture, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00166; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Tsymsh orchestra, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00167; Rascher, Andrew (Box 10)
    - Parents' Weekend, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00168; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Parents' Weekend, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00169; Sandberg, Stacia (Box 10)
    - Parents' Weekend, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00170; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Paving Prof. Row, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00171; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Peace and Justice Studies (symposium.-panel 3), 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00172; Ross, Linda (Box 10)
    - Peace and Justice Studies (symposium.# 2), 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00173; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Donna Penn--TLGBC Coordinator, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00174; Eisenberg, Laura (Box 10)
    - Nick's Pizza (Andrea's), 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00175; Condon, Jeff (Box 10)
    - Macphie--Plate--o--Shrimp, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00176; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Posters, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00177; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - Posters/Chalk--Illegal!, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00178; Kittredge, Wendy (Box 10)
    - Potholes/Ian Balfour, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00179; Scheidl, Peter (Box 10)
    - Professor Milburn, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00180; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Professor Mulholland, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00181; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Prof. John Perry--features, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00182; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Prof. Row Paving/work, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00183; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Pub Night, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00184; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Puppet Show, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00185; Skuws, Chris (Box 10)
    - Tom and Quartet, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00186; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Memorial Service for Michael Ratte, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00187; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Laura Reichus, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00188; De la Cruz, Cedric (Box 10)
    - Dean Reitman, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00189; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - REM album cover, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00190 (Box 10)
    - Rocky Horror, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00191; Newman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Rose -- Hodgdon, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00192; Denise (Box 10)
    - Rotondi, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00193; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Alex Schwartz--Senate Res, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00194; Starr, Ron (Box 10)
    - Senate, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00195; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - Senate Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00196; Quattro, De (Box 10)
    - Senate, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00197; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Senate Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00198; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - TCU Senate, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00199; Stevens, Chris (Box 10)
    - Senate, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00200; Besonen, Mark (Box 10)
    - Senate, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00201; Mode, R (Box 10)
    - Science Center, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00202; Stevens, Chris (Box 10)
    - Sexual Harassment Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00203; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Bill Shein, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00204; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Bill Shein, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00205; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Strange Photos for Bill Shein, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00206 (Box 10)
    - Bill Shein, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00207; Kohhundil, nat (Box 10)
    - Skateboarding (Medford Kids), 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00208; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Elenor Smeale, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00209; Bevnolven, Mark (Box 10)
    - Space Bridge, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00210; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Space Bridge, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00211; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Somerville Mtg., 1905; UA176.002.010.00001.00212; Schatz, Karl (Box 10)
    - UC South Africa Speaker/ Holiday Fair, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00213; Graver, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - South Africa Speaker, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00214; Besmen, Mark (Box 10)
    - Soviet Refusnik Letter, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00215; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Student Activities Fair, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00216; Love, Bill (Box 10)
    - Student Employment, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00217; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Student Government Rally, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00218; Newman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - Students W/ Moffat, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00219; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Sukkah, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00220; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Summer Construction, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00221; Dave's Buddy (Box 10)
    - Summer Construction, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00222; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Jeff Summit, 1905; UA176.002.010.00001.00223; Kulukundis, Natali (Box 10)
    - Supershow- Saraband, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00224 (Box 10)
    - Supershow, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00225; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Swimathon, 1905; UA176.002.010.00001.00226; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - TAB- Dedication, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00227; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - TAB Dedication, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00228; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - TAB Dedication, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00229; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - TAB Dedication, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00230; Snyder, Brian (Box 10)
    - Rob Takaki, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00231; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - TCB Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00232; Grauer, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - TCUJ Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00233; Grauer, Jonathan (Box 10)
    - TCUJ Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00234; Gilman, Stephen (Box 10)
    - TCUJ Meeting, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00235; Eisenberg, Laura (Box 10)
    - Tertulia, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00236; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Trios, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00237; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Tuftspeak, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00238; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Tuftspeak #1, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00239; Drower, Denise (Box 10)
    - Tuftspeak 2, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00240; Kulukundis, Natali (Box 10)
    - Tuftspeak 3, 1988; UA176.002.010.00001.00241; Bensonen, Mark (Box 10)